question_data = [
    {
    "category":"Science & Nature",
    "type":"boolean",
    "difficulty":"medium",
    "question":"The Neanderthals were a direct ancestor of modern humans.","correct_answer":"False",
    "incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"category":"Science & Nature",
     "type":"boolean",
     "difficulty":"medium",
     "question":"A person can get sunburned on a cloudy day.",
     "correct_answer":"True",
     "incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia is the irrational fear of long words.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The planet Mars has two moons orbiting it.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Like with the Neanderthals, Homo sapiens sapiens also interbred with the Denisovans.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Shrimp can swim backwards.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Anatomy considers the forms of macroscopic structures such as organs and organ systems.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In the periodic table, Potassium&#039;s symbol is the letter K.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Pneumonoultramicroscopicsilicovolcanoconiosis is a synonym for the disease known as silicosis.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"&quot;Tachycardia&quot; or &quot;Tachyarrhythmia&quot; refers to a resting heart-rate near or over 100 BPM.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]